{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269152735","data":{"timestamp":" 947269152735"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269164521","data":{"timestamp":" 947269164520"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269170133","data":{"timestamp":" 947269170132"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269170365","data":{"timestamp":" 947269170365"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269174722","data":{"timestamp":" 947269174722"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269175379","data":{"timestamp":" 947269175379"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269182588","data":{"timestamp":" 947269182588"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269195158","data":{"timestamp":" 947269195157"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269206185","data":{"timestamp":" 947269206185"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269216154","data":{"timestamp":" 947269216153"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269227174","data":{"timestamp":" 947269227174"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269274600","data":{"timestamp":" 947269274600"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269288875","data":{"timestamp":" 947269288875"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269298722","data":{"timestamp":" 947269298722"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269308013","data":{"timestamp":" 947269308013"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269322888","data":{"timestamp":" 947269322888"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269333786","data":{"timestamp":" 947269333786"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269346598","data":{"timestamp":" 947269346598"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269491230","data":{"timestamp":" 947269491230"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269497377","data":{"timestamp":" 947269497377"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269499177","data":{"timestamp":" 947269499177"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269557972","data":{"timestamp":" 947269557972"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269563066","data":{"timestamp":" 947269563066"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269569984","data":{"timestamp":" 947269569984"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269580654","data":{"timestamp":" 947269580652"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_211835"," gameId":" d0ccd4e6-fd37-4b1a-9887-2e1c5b2f537d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}